[
	{ "question": "Sul Sul", "answer": "Hello", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Dag Dag", "answer": "Goodbye", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Litzerga", "answer": "Thank you", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Geelfrob", "answer": "See you soon", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Whippna Choba Dog", "answer": "This is cool", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Boobasnot", "answer": "I don't like you", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Cuh Teekalo", "answer": "How's it going", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Renato", "answer": "Go away", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Oh Feebee Lay!", "answer": "I'm hungry", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "NooBoo", "answer": "Baby", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Lalo", "answer": "Milk", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Checkmar", "answer": "checkmate", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Za Woka Genava", "answer": "I think you are hot", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Ooh Be Gah", "answer": "Very Good", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Woofum", "answer": "Dog", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Xor", "answer": "Be", "M": 2 },
	{ "question": "Choo wagga choo choo!", "answer": "Something in the way", "M": 2 }
]
